How are you? You have ceased menstruation.
Yes.
As a result of drugs.
Yes, Man of God. She is on drugs; she takes drugs.
That is what I am saying. I said, it is as a result of drugs.
Yes, Man of God. She is addicted to drugs.
- She is addicted to drugs?
- Yes, Man of God.
This has affected her menstruation and given her chronic headaches.
Yes, Man of God. It is true. I came with her. She is my daughter's friend.
Ok. It's alright. Come on.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Get healed, in Jesus' name!
She is free.
Following her deliverance after the prophecy, the woman's menstruation began to flow
and she came back the next day to testify.
Makes Her Way To The Restroom
Ceased Menstruation Begins To Flow After Prophecy
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Praise the Lord!
My name is Hawa Nakamba.
I come from Zambia.
The persons standing beside me are my mother, my auntie and my cousin.
Last week Sunday when I came, the Prophet prophesied to me that I had ceased menstruation
due to drugs intake and that I also experienced headaches due to drugs.
I confirm the prophecy to be very true.
Hallelujah!
It all started three years ago when I was addicted to drugs in Zambia.
I used to take codeine.
In a day, I could take 5 to 6 bottles of codeine.
While my friends could only take one or two bottles of codeine, I could take 6 bottles.
I thank God because the way codeine used to affect me,
it made me not to be afraid of anyone.
I used to steal money from my mum just to buy codeine.
I would threaten her if she didn't give me money.
"Mum, give me money. I want to go and do something."
I could even steal from her.
I thank God. When the Prophet touched me on Sunday, I was delivered and I am free now.
When the Prophet touched me, I felt something moving (in my body).
I felt light.
Briefly tell us the consequences of the drugs you were taking before on your body and your health.
After taking the drugs, my menstruation seized.
I did not concentrate or listen to anyone.
When the Prophet just touched me, when he prayed for me,
immediately after, my menstruation started to flow.
Amen.
Hawa Nakamba & Family
Prophecy Testimony
My memory also came back. I slept well and I feel light, after the prophet prayed for me.
I feel very light and I am well now. I am free. Thank You, Jesus.
The urge for the drugs, and everthing of that lifestyle has gone?
It has gone.
This is what happened after the man of God prayed for me.
I had not seen my menstruation for so long.
But immediately after the man of God prayed for me, it started.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
We can see truly that our sister is delivered.
We saw in that word of prophecy as the man of God spoke to her,
she was still under the influence of the drugs; she was unable to even compose herself to respond.
But today, her memory is restored, her menstruation is restored, the addiction to drugs is gone
and she is here with her family to share this wonderful testimony.
Sister, what is your advice to people, especially young people all over the world watching you?
My advice goes to every youth watching me all over the world.
Stop taking drugs, it is not good.
Come to God, He can heal you and change your life.
Amen.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
RV: Mel Flowers 14/06/2018